Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Botany Records 1882-1972
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1891-1936
  - Subseries 7: Lantern Slides
    - New York, AEP-NYS2, Henry Chandler Cowles of the University of Chicago, Carl Schroter, and an unidentified member of the International Phytogeographic Excursion in America at the Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, New York AEP-NYS3, Henry Chandler Cowles of the University of Chicago and members of the International Phytogeographic Excursion in America, Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, New York AEP-NYS4, Members of the International Phytogeographic Excursion in America, Hempstead, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS5, The Cytologists group at the International Congress of Plant Sciences, Ithaca, New York AEP-NYS6, The Morphologists group at the International Congress of Plant Sciences, Ithaca, New York AEP-NYS7, Ecologists group at the International Congress of Plant Sciences, Ithaca, New York AEP-NYS8, Picea and Fagus in a mixed forest, Adirondack Mountains, New York AEP-NYS9, Alnus on clay with a gravel slope, Cooper Bluff, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS10, 120 foot high gravel summit, Cooper Bluff, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS11, Target Rock, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS12, A harbor from a sandspit, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS13, Ammophila on a sandspit, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS14, Ammophila and Hudsonia on a heath, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS15, Juncus and Spartina association, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS16, A seven foot stake with Salicornia and Spartina, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS17, The edge of a saltmarsh at low tide, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS18, A saltmarsh tension line, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS19, Hudsonia on a windward slope, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS20, The sandspit at Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYS21, The Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS22, The Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS23, Blackford Hall, Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS24, Eriophorum vaginatum in a swamp, Hempstead, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS25, Eriocaulon septangulare, Hempstead, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS26, A prairie at Hempstead, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS27, An eroding shore, Huntington, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS28, Chamaecyparis swamp, Merrick, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS29, Chamaecyparis in a swamp, Merrick, Long Island, New York AEP-NYS30, Taxus cuspidata var. hicksii, New York Botanical Garden, New York, New York AEP-NYS31, Herbaceous grounds, New York Botanical Garden, New York, New York AEP-NYS32, The Rose Garden, New York Botanical Garden, New York, New York AEP-NYS33, Chamaecyparis thyoides about a pond, Merrick Long Island, New York AEP-NYS37, A Scolopendrium vulgare habitat, Syracuse, New York AEP-NYS38, Scolopendrium vulgare, Syracuse, New York AEP-NYS39, Close view of Scolopendrium vulgare, Syracuse, New York (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 22)
    - North Carolina, AEP-NCS1, Pine on adune showing the influence of wind, Beaufort, North Carolina AEP-NCS2, An Abies balsamea forest with an undergrowth of Aspidium spinulosum var. dilatatum on the summit of Jones Knob, Jackson County, North Carolina AEP-NCS3, Mt. Mitchell, North Carolina denuded of Spruce and Balsam Fir at five thousand five hundred feet AEP-NCS4, Pinus taeda near Raleigh, North Carolina AEP-NCS5, Pinus taeda in contact with Quercus catesbaei on a sandridge, North Carolina AEP-NCS6, Quercus catesbaei and Aristida stricta on sandridges, North Carolina AEP-NCS7, Abies fraseri in the Great Smoky Mountains, North Carolina AEP-NCS8, Quercus catesbaei with Tillandsia usneoides on the lee of White Lake, North Carolina AEP-NCS9, Dwarfed Chestnut at an altitude of five thousand three hundred feet, North Carolina AEP-NCS10, Endemic Selaginella acanthonota and Cladonia, North Carolina AEP-NCS11, Endemic Selaginella acanthonota and Cladonia, North Carolina AEP-NCS12, Close view of Dionaea muscipula, North Carolina AEP-NCS13, Close view of Dionaea muscipula, North Carolina AEP-NCS14, Close view of Dionaea muscipula, North Carolina AEP-NCS15, Dimorphic leaves of Nymphaea sagittifolia, North Carolina AEP-NCS16, Picea australis at five thousand five hundred feet, North Carolina AEP-NCS17, Pinus echinata and Quercus spp. in the Appalachian foothills, North Carolina AEP-NCS18, Pinus palustris seedling, North Carolina AEP-NCS19, Pinus taeda on coastal plains, North Carolina AEP-NCS20, A mesophytic Oak forest, North Carolina AEP-NCS21, Three phases, Quercus and Carya climax in contact with Pinus Succession, North Carolina AEP-NCS22, Quercus catesbaei, North Carolina AEP-NCS23, Dwarfed Quercus rubra at an altitude of five thousand three hundred feet, North Carolina AEP-NCS24, A wind-formed Quercus virginiana, North Carolina AEP-NCS25, Uniola spp. on coastal dunes, North Carolina (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 22)
    - Ohio, AEP-OHS1, Winter at Oberlin College campus, Oberlin, Ohio AEP-OHS2, A River steamer, Ohio AEP-OHS3, Branches and fruit of a Ginkgo biloba, Elyria, Ohio AEP-OHS4, Branches and fruit of a Ginkgo biloba, Elyria, Ohio AEP-OHS5, A Ginkgo biloba on the lawn of William Graves Sharp, American ambassador to France, 1914-1919, Elyria, Ohio AEP-OHS6, Ginkgo biloba on the lawn of William Graves Sharp, American ambassador to France, 1914-1919, Elyria, Ohio (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 22)
    - Oklahoma, AEP-OKS1, Prosopis with shoots from exposed roots on an eroding floodplain dune near Devol, Oklahoma AEP-OKS2, Prosopis with shoots from exposed roots on an eroding floodplain dune near Devol, Oklahoma AEP-OKS3, Juniperus virginiana on a cliff, Acer saccharum and Quercus shumardii in a river bottom, and Bouteloua and Andropogon on an upland, Devils Canyon, Oklahoma AEP-OKS4, Juniperus virginiana and Quercus marilandica near Devils Canyon, Oklahoma AEP-OKS5, Wind contorted Cottonwood near Grandfield, Oklahoma AEP-OKS6, In the Red River Valley near Grandfield, Oklahoma AEP-OKS7, In the Red River Valley near Grandfield, Oklahoma AEP-OKS8, A prairie with eight foot high Andropogon furcatus, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS9, Amsonia tabernaemontana on a gravel floodplain of the Arkansas River, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS10, An Andropogon furcatus prairie with conspicuous Silphium laciniatum in July, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS11, An Andropogon furcatus prairie in October, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS12, An ungrazed and overgrazed Andropogon furcatus prairie in July with Ptilimnium nuttallii, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS13, Diospyros virginiana in a prairie and forest transition, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS14, Jussiaea diffusa forming a mat over a prairie pond with Salix nigra, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS15, An Oak, Hickory, and Pine forest on a hillside, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS16, An open Oak and Hickory forest, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS17, Seedling of Salix and Populus on a sand floodplain of the Canadian River, Muskogee County, Oklahoma AEP-OKS19, A prairie showing natural mounds near Wilburton, Oklahoma AEP-OKS20, Quercus spp. on hills with a cleared field in the valley, southeastern Oklahoma AEP-OKS21, Andropogon furcatus with Helianthus mollis, Oklahoma AEP-OKS22, A Willow zone on a floodplain, Oklahoma (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 22)
    - Oregon, AEP-ORS2, Abies magnifica with the lichen Evernia, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS3, Abies lasiocarpa and Pinus murrayana, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS4, Dicentra formosa, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS5, A stand of Pinus lambertiana, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS6, The trunk of a Pinus lambertiana, Crater Lake National Park, Oregon AEP-ORS7, A stand of Pinus lambertiana, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS8, George Damon Fuller of the University of Chicago Department of Botany kneeling near a Pinus monticola, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS9, Pinus murrayana, Crater Lake National Park, Oregon AEP-ORS10, Trunks of Pseudotsuga, Crater Lake National Park, Oregon AEP-ORS11, Tsuga and Abies on Wizard Island, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS12, Tsuga mertensiana, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS13, Tsuga mertensiana, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS14, Wizard Island, Crater Lake, Oregon AEP-ORS21, Arctostaphylos glauca and Ceanothus, Medford, Oregon AEP-ORS22, Phoradendron flavescens on Quercus garryana, Medford, Oregon AEP-ORS23, Pinus ponderosa and Quercus garryana with Chaparral, Medford, Oregon AEP-ORS24, Quercus garryana and Arctostaphylos, Medford, Oregon AEP-ORS25, Prairie at Medford, Oregon AEP-ORS26, A forest of Tsuga mertensiana near the inn, Mt. Hood, Oregon AEP-ORS27, Pine bent by the weight of snow, Mt. Hood, Oregon AEP-ORS29, Hemlock krummholz, Mt. Hood, Oregon AEP-ORS30, An extreme timberline, Mt. Hood, Oregon AEP-ORS33, Crevasses on Mt. Hood, Oregon AEP-ORS34, Mt. Hood, Oregon in summer AEP-ORS48, A 250 foot high Pseudotsuga mucronata near Portland, Oregon AEP-ORS49, Pinus ponderosa and Pinus lambertiana, Prospect, Oregon AEP-ORS50, A man and woman with a covered wagon, Prospect, Oregon AEP-ORS51, A view of a Picea breweriana, Oregon AEP-ORS52, Mt. Hood, Oregon in summer AEP-ORS53, Picea sitchensis in a coastal forest, Oregon (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 23)
    - Pennsylvania, AEP-PAS1, Flowering Dogwood, Delaware County, Pennsylvania AEP-PAS2, An old saw mill, Marklesburg, Pennsylvania AEP-PAS3, The Pittsburgh flood, Pennsylvania AEP-PAS4, The Pittsburgh flood, Pennsylvania AEP-PAS5, The Pittsburgh flood, Pennsylvania AEP-PAS6, The second growth of a Castanea dentata showing the formation of rings, Western Pennsylvania AEP-PAS7, Beech, Northern White Oak, and Chestnut in a climax forest, Western Pennsylvania AEP-PAS8, Eroding skid trails and a logged-over area, Pennsylvania (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 23)
    - South Dakota, AEP-SDS1, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS2, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS3, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS4, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS5, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS6, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS7, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS8, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS9, Argemone intermedia, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS10, Artemisia tridentata, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS11, Koeleria cristata, Agropyron smithii, Agropyron spicata, Buchloe dactyloides and Stipa comata, Reynolds Prairie, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS12, A Willow to White Spruce to Ponderosa Pine transition, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS13, Xerophytes on limestone, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS14, Ragged Top Mountain, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS15, Near Lead, South Dakota looking down Gold Run in the Black Hills, AEP-SDS16, Open mining in Lead, South Dakota AEP-SDS17, Down Spearfish Canyon, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS18, The Badlands, South Dakota AEP-SDS19, Spearfish Falls, Black Hills, South Dakota AEP-SDS20, Pinus ponderosa on rocky ridge and Quercus macrocarpa, Ulmus americana and Fraxinus lanceolata in ravines in an area between Sturgis and Whitewood, South Dakota (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 23)
    - Tennessee, AEP-TNS4, Erosion at Copper Hill, Ducktown, Tennessee due to injuries from copper fumes AEP-TNS5, Erosion at Copper Hill, Ducktown, Tennessee due to injuries from copper fumes AEP-TNS6, Erosion at Ducktown, Tennessee due to injuries from copper fumes AEP-TNS10, Ilex opaca, La Follette, Tennessee AEP-TNS16, Liriodendron tulipifera and Fagus grandifolia in a mixed forest, Pickett County, Tennessee AEP-TNS17, A mixed slope forest of Liriodendron tulipifera, Carya ovata, Magnolia acuminata, Castanea dentata, and Betula lenta, Rock Creek, Tennessee AEP-TNS18, Nelumbo lutea with dead Taxodium in the central northeast corner of Reelfoot Lake, Tennessee AEP-TNS19, Nelumbo lutea with Taxodium in Reelfoot Lake, Tennessee AEP-TNS20, Nelumbo lutea with Taxodium in the southeast corner of Reelfoot Lake, Tennessee AEP-TNS21, A view of a Betula lenta trunk at Beech Gap, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS22, A Rhododendron catawbiense thicket on the trail from Mt. Le Conte to Beech Gap, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS24, Le Conte Falls, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS25, Polypodium vulgare on a leaning Birch, Le Conte Trail, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS26, A ridge with a Rhododendron thicket on the summit seen to the right of Le Conte Trail, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS27, Young hemlocks on logs and rocks, Le Conte Trail, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS28, Balsam Fir forest on Mt. Le Conte, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS29, Balsam Fir forest with a moss carpet of Hylocomium prolificum and Hypnum crista-castensis, Mt. Le Conte, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS30, Balsam Fir forest, Mt. Le Conte, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS31, View of Fir covered mountains with smoky clouds drifting across from Mt. Le Conte, Great Smoky Mountain National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS34, On top of Mt. Le Conte, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS35, The alteration of a slope at Little River above Elkmont, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS36, Hemlock and Rhododendron at Norton Creek, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS37, Dogwood, Hemlock, and Rhododendron at Roaring Fork near Spruce Flats Mill, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS38, The Pigeon River with Balsam Point in the distance, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS39, Northern Red Oak with a circumference of twenty-one feet above Spruce Flats near Roaring Fork, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS40, Leucothoe on a steep north slope at Roaring Fork, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS41, Polypodium and rocks along the trail to Roaring Fork, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS42, Hemlock and Rhododendron on the trail down the north branch of Roaring Fork, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS43, Roaring Fork just below the junction with the Baskins Creek Trail, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS44, A mill dam and mill, Roaring Fork near Gatlinburg, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS45, Roaring Fork near Spruce Flats School down stream from the swinging bridge at the mill, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS46, Hemlock forest with Rhododendron, Spruce Flats, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS47, Carolina Silverbell at Spruce Flats, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS48, Halesia carolina in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS49, Mount Le Conte from Spruce Flats School, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS50, Interior of a mill, Spruce Flats School, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS51, North and south slope forests of Beech and Maple and of Oak and Pine, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS52, Halesia carolina, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS53, Quercus rubra, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS54, Liriodendron tulipifera, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS55, Tsuga and Rhododendron, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS56, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS57, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS58, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS59, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS60, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS61, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS62, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee AEP-TNS63, George Damon Fuller, Orpheus Schantz, and students of a University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawers 23-24)
    - Texas, AEP-TXS1, Andropogon on a sand bar flood plain of the Red River, Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS2, Cottonwood and Prickly Ash dune on the Red River flood plain, Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS3, A foredune invading a Salix sand bar flood plain at the Red River, Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS4, Eroding floodplain dunes of the Red River near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS5, Eroding floodplain dunes of the Red River near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS6, Eroding floodplain dunes of the Red River near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS7, Eroding floodplain dunes of the Red River near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS8, An antecedent Cottonwood on eroding floodplain dunes of the Red River, Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS9, A prairie upland near the Red River, Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS10, A Red River oil field near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS11, A Red River oil field near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS12, A Red River oil field near Burkburnett, Texas AEP-TXS13, A Yucca desert, Comstock, Texas AEP-TXS14, An infantry camp, Meyers Canyon, Texas AEP-TXS16, Orlin Biddulph with Harrison and Turner at the Pecos River, Texas AEP-TXS18, A young Carya illinoinensis in fruit, San Antonio, Texas AEP-TXS19, A foredune with an annual of the family Boraginaceae on the Red River floodplain, Vernon, Texas AEP-TXS20, Mesquite savanna near Vernon, Texas AEP-TXS21, Mesquite savanna near Vernon, Texas AEP-TXS22, A young Pinus palustris, Texas AEP-TXS23, Prosopis juliflora, Texas AEP-TXS24, Spanish Moss on Oak, Texas AEP-TXS25, Orlin Biddulph with Harrison and Turner in west Texas (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 24)